<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<databaseChangeLog
        xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
        xmlns="http://www.liquibase.org/xml/ns/dbchangelog"
        xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.liquibase.org/xml/ns/dbchangelog http://www.liquibase.org/xml/ns/dbchangelog/dbchangelog-3.1.xsd">

    <!-- Заполнение таблицы bicycles данными -->
    <changeSet author="FeinIV" id="27122021_filling_bicycle_table_WOMAN">
        <sql>
            INSERT INTO bicycles (
            img_addr, name, manufacturer, price, discount, description, level, frame_material,
            fork_type, fork_material, fork_description, number_of_speeds, type, weight, wheel_diameter, rim_type,
            break_type, sex, availability
            )
            VALUES
            ('assets/images/bicycles_woman/Stels Navigator 245 26 Z010 (2020).jpg', 'Stels Navigator 245 26 Z010 (2020)', 'Stels', 15210, 15,
            'Women''s road bike without gear shifting. Technical features: durable steel frame
            Hi-Ten, rigid steel fork, double aluminum rims, foot pedal brakes, chain guard, long fenders,
            trunk, front basket, bell. Suitable for pleasure riding on highways and flat country roads.
            Wheel diameter - 26 inches. Weight - 16.6 kg.',
            1, 'Steel', 'Regid', 'Steel', 'Regid steel fork from Stels manufacturer', '1', 'WOMAN', '17.43', '26 inches',
            'Double', 'Foot pedal', 'Female', 'true'
            ),

            ('assets/images/bicycles_woman/Stels Navigator 300 Lady 28 Z010 (2018).jpg', 'Stels Navigator 300 Lady 28 Z010 (2018)', 'Stels', 13530, 28,
            'Women''s road bike without gear shifting. Specifications: Hi-Ten steel frame, rigid steel fork,
            double aluminum rims, foot pedal brakes, chain guard, long fenders, trunk, bell. Suitable for walking
            skiing in urban conditions and on simple routes in the forest. Wheel diameter - 28 inches. Weight - 17.43 kg.',
            1, 'Steel', 'Regid', 'Steel', 'Regid steel fork from Stels manufacturer', '1', 'WOMAN', '17.43', '28 inches',
            'Double', 'Foot pedal', 'Female', 'false'
            ),

            ('assets/images/bicycles_woman/Stels Navigator 325 28 Z010 (2019).jpg', 'Stels Navigator 325 28 Z010 (2019)', 'Stels', 13530, 28,
            'Women''s road bike without gear shifting. Technical features: Hi-Ten steel frame, rigid
            steel fork, double aluminum rims, foot pedal brakes, chain guard, long fenders, rack,
            front basket, bell. Suitable for recreational skiing in urban areas and on easy routes in the forest.
            Wheel diameter - 28 inches. Weight - 17.3 kg.',
            1, 'Steel', 'Regid', 'Steel', 'Regid steel fork from Stels manufacturer', '1', 'WOMAN', '17.3', '28 inches',
            'Double', 'Foot pedal', 'Female', 'true'
            ),

            ('assets/images/bicycles_woman/Stels Navigator 345 28 Z010 (2018).jpg', 'Stels Navigator 345 28 Z010 (2018)', 'Stels', 14380, 25,
            'Women''s road bike without gear shifting. Specifications: Hi-Ten steel frame, rigid steel fork,
            double aluminum rims, foot pedal brakes, chain guard, long fenders, rack, comfort saddle, bell. Fits
            for recreational skiing in urban areas and along simple routes in the forest. Wheel diameter - 28 inches. Weight - 17.31 kg.',
            1, 'Steel', 'Regid', 'Steel', 'Regid steel fork from Stels manufacturer', '1', 'WOMAN', '17.31', '28 inches',
            'Double', 'Foot pedal', 'Female', 'false'
            ),

            ('assets/images/bicycles_woman/Stinger Cruiser Lady 26 (2021).jpg', 'Stinger Cruiser Lady 26 (2021)', 'Stinger', 22700, 15,
            'Comfortable female cruiser without gear shifting. Specifications: 6061 aluminum frame, rigid steel fork
            Stinger Rigid, Felgebeiter HAC21 double rims, front STG V-Brake, rear foot brake, chain guard, long fenders,
            comfortable saddle, bell, footrest. Suitable for comfortable riding in parks and city streets. Wheel diameter - 26 inches.
            Weight - 16.3 kg.',
            1, 'Aluminum', 'Regid', 'Steel', 'Regid steel fork from Stinger manufacturer', '1', 'WOMAN', '16.3', '26 inches',
            'Double', 'Foot pedal', 'Female', 'true'
            )

        </sql>
    </changeSet>

    <!-- Заполнение таблицы bicycles детскими велосипедами -->
    <changeSet author="FeinIV" id="29122021_filling_bicycle_table_CHILDREN">
        <sql>
            INSERT INTO bicycles (
            img_addr, name, manufacturer, price, discount, description, level, frame_material,
            fork_type, fork_material, fork_description, number_of_speeds, type, weight, wheel_diameter, rim_type,
            break_type, sex, availability
            )
            VALUES
            ('assets/images/bicycles_children/Stels Powerkid Boy V020 (2020).jpg', 'Stels Powerkid Boy V020 (2020)', 'Stels', 4040, 15,
            'A balance bike designed for children aged one and a half to three years. Technical features: durable Hi-Ten steel frame,
            rigid steel fork, single aluminum rims, no brakes. Suitable for learning and light walking.
            Wheel diameter - 12 inches. Weight - 5.3 kg.',
            1, 'Steel', 'Regid', 'Steel', 'Regid steel fork from Stels manufacturer', '0', 'CHILDREN', '5.3', '12 inches',
            'Aluminum, single', 'No brakes', 'Unisex', 'false'
            ),

            ('assets/images/bicycles_children/Polisport Balance bike (2020).jpg', 'Polisport Balance bike (2020)', 'Polisport', 4600, 20,
            'A balance bike designed for children aged one and a half to three years. Technical features: plastic frame,
            rigid plastic fork, reinforced plastic rims, brakes are not provided by the design (braking by feet).
            The maximum load is 25 kg. Suitable for learning and light walking. Wheel diameter - 9.5 inches. Weight - 3 kg.',
            1, 'Plastic', 'Regid', 'Plastic', 'Regid plastic fork from Polisport manufacturer', '1', 'CHILDREN', '3', '10 inches',
            'Plastic, reinforced', 'No brakes', 'Unisex', 'true'
            ),

            ('assets/images/bicycles_children/Novatrack Urban 16 (2019).jpg', 'Novatrack Urban 16 (2019)', 'Novatrack', 6600, 21,
            'Bicycle intended for children aged two to four years, without gear shifting.
            Technical features: Hi-Ten steel frame, rigid steel fork, single aluminum rims, foot pedal brakes,
            chain protection, removable side wheels, fenders, padded steering wheel, bell. Suitable for learning and light walking.
            Wheel diameter - 16 inches. Weight - 9.8 kg.',
            1, 'Steel', 'Regid', 'Steel', 'Regid steel fork from Novatrack manufacturer', '1', 'CHILDREN', '9.8', '16 inches',
            'Single, aluminum', 'Foot pedal', 'Unisex', 'false'
            ),

            ('assets/images/bicycles_children/Stels Flyte 14 Z011 (2018).jpg', 'Stels Flyte 14 Z011 (2018)', 'Stels', 8000, 36,
            'Bicycle intended for children aged two to four years, without gear shifting. Technical features:
            Hi-Ten steel frame, rigid steel fork, single aluminum rims, foot pedal brakes, chain guard, long
            fenders, trunk, bell. Suitable for learning and light walking. Wheel diameter - 14 inches. Weight - 10.4 kg.',
            1, 'Steel', 'Regid', 'Steel', 'Regid steel fork from Stels manufacturer', '1', 'CHILDREN', '10.4', '14 inches',
            'Single, aluminum', 'Foot pedal', 'Unisex', 'true'
            ),

            ('assets/images/bicycles_children/Stels Pilot 200 Gent 20 Z010 (2019).jpg', 'Stels Pilot 200 Gent 20 Z010 (2019)', 'Stels', 22700, 15,
            'A bike designed for children aged five to nine, without gear shifting. Technical features:
            Hi-Ten steel frame, rigid steel fork, double aluminum rims, foot pedal brakes, full chain guard, steel
            wings, call. Suitable for learning and recreational riding in urban environments. Wheel diameter - 20 inches. Weight - 12.5 kg.',
            1, 'Steel', 'Regid', 'Steel', 'Regid steel fork from Stels manufacturer', '1', 'CHILDREN', '12.5', '20 inches',
            'Double', 'Foot pedal and front V-brake', 'Unisex', 'false'
            )

        </sql>
    </changeSet>

    <!-- Заполнение таблицы bicycles дорожными велосипедами -->
    <changeSet author="FeinIV" id="29122021_filling_bicycle_table_ROAD">
        <sql>
            INSERT INTO bicycles (
            img_addr, name, manufacturer, price, discount, description, level, frame_material,
            fork_type, fork_material, fork_description, number_of_speeds, type, weight, wheel_diameter, rim_type,
            break_type, sex, availability
            )
            VALUES
            ('assets/images/bicycles_road/Altair City 28 high (2022).jpg', 'Altair City 28 high (2022)', 'Altair', 9360, 0,
            'An entry-level road bike without shifting. Technical features: Hi-Ten steel frame,
            Rigid steel Hi-Ten fork, double aluminum rims, foot pedal brakes, long fenders, chain guard, rack.
            Suitable for pleasure riding on the highway and light rough terrain. Wheel diameter - 28 inches. Weight - 18 kg.',
            1, 'Steel', 'Regid', 'Steel', 'Regid steel fork from Altair manufacturer', '0', 'ROAD', '18', '28 inches',
            'Double', 'Foot pedal', 'Unisex', 'false'
            ),

            ('assets/images/bicycles_road/Bear Bike Stockholm (2021).jpg', 'Bear Bike Stockholm (2021)', 'Bear Bike', 25000, 20,
            'A road bike for riding in an urban environment without changing gears. Technical features: Hi-ten steel frame,
            rigid steel fork, double aluminum rims, durable Tektro R315 caliper rim brakes.
            Suitable for walking and sports riding in urban environments. Wheel diameter - 28 inches. Weight - 10 kg.',
            1, 'Steel', 'Regid', 'Steel', 'Regid steel fork from Bear Bike manufacturer', '1', 'ROAD', '10', '28 inches',
            'Double', 'V-brakes', 'Unisex', 'true'
            ),

            ('assets/images/bicycles_road/Stels Navigator 800 Gent 28 V010 (2021).jpg', 'Stels Navigator 800 Gent 28 V010 (2021)', 'Stels', 33200, 15,
            'Touring road bike with Microshift attachments, 21 speeds. Technical features: aluminum frame, suspension fork,
            double aluminum rims, reliable V-brake rim brakes, plastic chain guard, long fenders, rack, adjustable stem, footrest.
            Suitable for tourist and recreational riding on various roads and rough terrain. Wheel diameter - 28 inches. Weight - 16.4 kg.',
            2, 'Aluminum', 'Spring-elastomeric', 'Aluminum', 'Spring-elastomeric, stroke 60 mm', '21', 'ROAD', '16.4', '16 inches',
            'Double', 'V-brakes', 'Unisex', 'false'
            ),

            ('assets/images/bicycles_road/Merida Speeder GT-R (2021).jpg', 'Merida Speeder GT-R (2021)', 'Merida', 43870, 0,
            'Road bike for riding in an urban environment with Shimano amateur equipment, 16 speeds.
            Tech features: Speeder TFS aluminum frame, Merida Speeder CF2 rigid carbon fork, dual
            Merida Comp SL rims, AS2.2D caliper mechanical rim brakes. Suitable for walking and sports
            skiing in urban areas. Wheel diameter - 28 inches. Weight - 10.2 kg.',
            2, 'Aluminum', 'Regid', 'Carbon', 'MERIDA SPEEDER CF2 Tapered; MAT carbon', '16', 'ROAD', '10.2', '28 inches',
            'Single', 'AS2.2D', 'Unisex', 'true'
            ),

            ('assets/images/bicycles_road/Trek Dual Sport 3 (2019).jpg', 'Trek Dual Sport 3 (2019)', 'Trek', 51400, 10,
            'Road bike for riding in an urban environment with equipment of the highest amateur class Shimano, 27 speeds.
            Tech Features: Alpha Gold Aluminum Frame, SR Suntour NEX Suspension Fork, Dual Rims
            Bontrager Approved, Shimano MT200 hydraulic disc brakes. Suitable for walking and
            sports skating in urban environments. Wheel diameter - 28 inches. Weight - 13.5 kg.',
            2, 'Aluminum', 'Spring-elastomeric', 'Aluminum', 'Spring-elastomeric, stroke 63 mm', '27', 'ROAD', '13.5', '28 inches',
            'Double', 'Disc hydraulic', 'Unisex', 'true'
            )

        </sql>
    </changeSet>

    <!-- Заполнение таблицы bicycles комфортными велосипедами -->
    <changeSet author="FeinIV" id="29122021_filling_bicycle_table_COMFORT">
        <sql>
            INSERT INTO bicycles (
            img_addr, name, manufacturer, price, discount, description, level, frame_material,
            fork_type, fork_material, fork_description, number_of_speeds, type, weight, wheel_diameter, rim_type,
            break_type, sex, availability
            )
            VALUES
            ('assets/images/bicycles_comfort/Welt King AL 3 (2021).jpg', 'Welt King AL 3 (2021)', 'Welt', 34000, 15,
            'Comfortable cruiser with Shimano planetary equipment, 3 speeds. Technical features:
            Alloy 6061 aluminum frame, Rigid steel fork, double aluminum rims, front brake
            - Artek 218DG V-brake, rear - foot, chain protection, long fenders, trunk, comfortable saddle, footboard.
            Suitable for comfortable riding in parks and city streets. Wheel diameter - 26 inches. Weight - 17.5 kg.',
            2, 'Aluminum', 'Regid', 'Steel', 'Regid steel fork from Welt manufacturer', '3', 'COMFORT', '17.5', '26 inches',
            'Double', 'Foot pedal and V-brake', 'Unisex', 'false'
            ),

            ('assets/images/bicycles_comfort/Merida Crossway 40 (2021).jpg', 'Merida Crossway 40 (2021)', 'Merida', 48790, 0,
            'Comfortable road bike equipped with amateur Shimano equipment, 27 speeds. Technical features:
            Crossway Speed aluminum frame, SR Suntour NEX HLO suspension fork with 63mm travel, Merida CC dual rims,
            Shimano ST-EF505 hydraulic disc brakes, cushioned seatpost, adjustable stem. Fits
            for comfortable riding in parks, city streets and on routes of medium difficulty in the forest. Wheel diameter - 28 inches. Weight - 14 kg.',
            2, 'Aluminum', 'Spring-elastomeric', 'Aluminum', 'Spring-elastomeric, stroke 63 mm', '27', 'COMFORT', '14', '28 inches',
            'Double', 'Disc hydraulic', 'Unisex', 'true'
            ),

            ('assets/images/bicycles_comfort/Giant Sedona DX (2021).jpg', 'Giant Sedona DX (2021)', 'Giant', 54100, 0,
            'Comfortable bike with equipment of the initial amateur class Shimano, 16 speeds. Technical features:
            ALUXX-Grade Aluminum frame, SR Suntour XCT suspension fork, Giant GX Disc dual rims, mechanical disc
            brakes, cushioned seatpost, adjustable stem, comfortable saddle. Suitable for comfortable riding in the parks,
            city streets and along routes of medium difficulty in the forest. Wheel diameter - 26 inches. Weight - 15.2 kg.',
            2, 'Aluminum', 'Spring-elastomeric', 'Aluminum', 'Spring-elastomeric, stroke 80 mm', '21', 'COMFORT', '15.2', '26 inches',
            'Double', 'Disc mechanic', 'Unisex', 'false'
            ),

            ('assets/images/bicycles_comfort/Format 5512 26 (2021).jpg', 'Format 5512 26 (2021)', 'Format', 36620, 0,
            'Comfortable cruiser with Shimano planetary equipment, 3 speeds. Technical features:
            City/Cruiser aluminum frame, rigid steel fork, double Weinmann Amuz rims, foot pedal brakes,
            characterized by the greatest ease of use and reliability, wings. Suitable for comfortable riding in the parks
            and city streets. Wheel diameter 26 inches. Weight - 14.2 kg.',
            2, 'Aluminum', 'Regid', 'Steel', 'Regid steel fork from Welt manufacturer', '3', 'COMFORT', '14.2', '26 inches',
            'Double', 'Foot pedal', 'Unisex', 'true'
            ),

            ('assets/images/bicycles_comfort/Giant Simple Single (2009).jpg', 'Giant Simple Single (2009)', 'Giant', 10383, 5,
            'Comfort hardtail with Shimano Tourney entry-level equipment, 1 speed, aluminum frame
            ALUXX-Grade Aluminum, rigid front fork, mechanical rim brakes, dual rims. Suitable for comfortable riding style',
            2, 'Aluminum', 'Regid', 'Steel', 'Regid steel fork from Giant manufacturer', '1', 'COMFORT', '14', '26 inches',
            'Double', 'Foot pedal', 'Unisex', 'false'
            )

        </sql>
    </changeSet>

    <!-- Заполнение таблицы bicycles гравийными велосипедами -->
    <changeSet author="FeinIV" id="29122021_filling_bicycle_table_GRAVEL">
        <sql>
            INSERT INTO bicycles (
            img_addr, name, manufacturer, price, discount, description, level, frame_material,
            fork_type, fork_material, fork_description, number_of_speeds, type, weight, wheel_diameter, rim_type,
            break_type, sex, availability
            )
            VALUES
            ('assets/images/bicycles_gravel/Rush Hour GS 385 (2021).jpg', 'Rush Hour GS 385 (2021)', 'Rush Hour', 41260, 0,
            'Gravel bike with Shimano entry-level equipment, 16 speeds. Technical features:
            aluminum frame, rigid aluminum fork, double aluminum rims, Ruiput DS310A mechanical disc brakes.
            Suitable for active driving on various roads and rough terrain. Wheel diameter - 28 inches. Weight - 13.8 kg.',
            2, 'Aluminum', 'Regid', 'Aluminum', 'Regid aluminum fork from Rush Hour manufacturer', '16', 'GRAVEL', '13.8', '28 inches',
            'Double', 'Disc mechanic', 'Unisex', 'true'
            ),

            ('assets/images/bicycles_gravel/Format 5222 CF (2021).jpg', 'Format 5222 CF (2021)', 'Format', 89900, 0,
            'Gravel bike with Shimano entry-level equipment, 16 speeds. Technical features:
            700C Tour 4130 Cr-mo chromoly frame, rigid fork, Weinmann Impulse double rims, mechanical disc brakes
            TRP Spyre. Suitable for active driving on various roads and rough terrain. Wheel diameter - 28 inches. Weight - 15 kg.',
            2, 'CrMo', 'Regid', 'CrMo', 'Regid CrMo fork from Format manufacturer', '16', 'GRAVEL', '15', '28 inches',
            'Double', 'Disc mechanic', 'Unisex', 'false'
            ),

            ('assets/images/bicycles_gravel/Merida Silex 200 (2020).jpg', 'Merida Silex 200 (2020)', 'Merida', 73426, 0,
            'Gravel bike equipped with Shimano hobby equipment, 18 speeds. Technical features:
            Silex Lite aluminum frame, Merida Silex CF2 rigid fork, Merida Comp SL dual rims,
            disc mechanical brakes Promax DSK-330R. Suitable for active driving on various roads and rough terrain.
            Wheel diameter - 28 inches. Weight - 10.45 kg.',
            3, 'Aluminum', 'Regid', 'Aluminum', 'Merida Silex CF2', '18', 'GRAVEL', '10.45', '28 inches',
            'Double', 'Disc mechanic', 'Unisex', 'false'
            ),

            ('assets/images/bicycles_gravel/Cube Nuroad EX (2022).jpg', 'Cube Nuroad EX (2022)', 'Cube', 158400, 0,
            'Gravel bike with Shimano professional equipment, 11 speeds. Technical features:
            Aluminum 6061 T6 Superlite frame, CUBE Nuroad Disc rigid fork, CUBE GR 2.3 dual rims,
            Shimano GRX BR-RX400 hydraulic disc brakes. Suitable for active driving on various roads and
            rough terrain. Wheel diameter - 28 inches. Weight - 10.2 kg.',
            5, 'Aluminum', 'Regid', 'Carbon', 'CUBE Nuroad Flat Mount Disc, Full Carbon', '11', 'GRAVEL', '10.2', '28 inches',
            'Double', 'Disc hydraulic', 'Unisex', 'true'
            ),

            ('assets/images/bicycles_gravel/Mongoose Guide Comp (2019).jpg', 'Mongoose Guide Comp (2019)', 'Mongoose', 82300, 0,
            'Cyclocross bike with Shimano pre-professional equipment, 20 speeds. Technical features:
            aluminum 700c adventure geometry frame, Mongoose 700c carbon rigid fork, dual
            WTB ST-19 aluminum double wall rims, Shimano BR-S405 hydraulic disc brakes. Fits
            for sports skating in the discipline of cyclocross. Wheel diameter - 28 inches. Weight - 10 kg.',
            4, 'Aluminum', 'Regid', 'Carbon', 'Mongoose 700c carbon with aluminum steerer', '20', 'GRAVEL', '10', '28 inches',
            'Double', 'Disc hydraulic', 'Unisex', 'false'
            )

        </sql>
    </changeSet>

</databaseChangeLog>
