<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<databaseChangeLog
        xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
        xmlns="http://www.liquibase.org/xml/ns/dbchangelog"
        xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.liquibase.org/xml/ns/dbchangelog http://www.liquibase.org/xml/ns/dbchangelog/dbchangelog-3.1.xsd">

    <!-- Заполнение таблицы spares амортизаторами -->
    <changeSet author="FeinIV" id="20220115_filling_spares_table_SHOCK">
        <sql>
            INSERT INTO spares (
            img_addr, name, manufacturer, price, discount, type, description,
            material, development_country, manufacturer_country, color, size, weight, features, availability
            )
            VALUES
            ('assets/images/spares_shocks/DT Swiss M210 200 50mm LR OE.jpg', 'DT Swiss M210 200 50mm LR OE', 'DT Swiss', 10200, 5, 'SHOCK',
            'The Swiss company DT Swiss is a recognized manufacturer of bicycle components and knows a lot about
            making shock absorbers and forks. The M210 rear shock is designed for All Mountain and Enduro riding.
            Made from durable anodized aluminum alloy. Housing size along the axes: 200 mm. Travel - 50 mm.',
            'Aluminum', 'Switzerland', 'Switzerland', 'black, red, grey', null, '240 g.', 'oil-air', 'true'
            ),

            ('assets/images/spares_shocks/KS-290.jpg', 'KS-290', 'KS', 1890, 0, 'SHOCK',
            'Inexpensive rear shock absorber Kind Shock KS-290 is designed for amateur full-suspension. 38mm travel is enough
            to overcome bumps and small bumps in the road. By design, the KS-290 is a spring-oil shock absorber. The length between axles is 165 mm.',
            null, 'China', 'China', 'black', null, null, 'oil-air', 'false'
            ),

            ('assets/images/spares_shocks/KS-291.jpg', 'KS-291', 'KS', 3400, 5, 'SHOCK',
            'KS-291 Kind Shock Spring Air/Oil Rear Shock with adjustable spring compression and rebound.
            The role of the spring in it is performed by cartridges with air, which is pumped into it under high pressure. The more air pressure, the stiffer the shock absorber.',
            null, 'China', 'China', 'black', null, '300 g.', null, 'true'
            )
        </sql>
    </changeSet>

    <!-- Заполнение таблицы spares каретками -->
    <changeSet author="FeinIV" id="20220115_filling_spares_table_CARRIAGE">
        <sql>
            INSERT INTO spares (
            img_addr, name, manufacturer, price, discount, type, description,
            material, development_country, manufacturer_country, color, size, weight, features, availability
            )
            VALUES
            ('assets/images/spares_carriages/Shimano BB-ES51 68 121.jpg', 'Shimano BB-ES51 68 121', 'Shimano', 2440, 5, 'CARRIAGE',
            'The Shimano BB-ES51 is a durable, load-proven bottom bracket designed for mountain bikes.
            It consists of a durable nickel-plated housing, into which bearings are hermetically pressed, as well as a chromoly axle with splined fastening for connecting rods. Standard - Octalink.',
            'Nickel-plated body / Cr-Mo axle', 'Japan', 'China', 'black / silver', '68/121 mm', null, 'Octalink, sealed bearings, without bolts', 'true'
            ),

            ('assets/images/spares_carriages/Shimano Saint, BB80, 83mm, BSA.jpg', 'Shimano Saint, BB80, 83мм, BSA', 'Shimano', 2190, 0, 'CARRIAGE',
            'The Shimano Saint bottom bracket is designed specifically for the extreme disciplines of mountain biking. Integrated carriage
            type BB80 consists of two cups with bearings pressed into them, screwed into the bottom bracket shell.
            There is a plastic spacer between the cups. This design avoids unnecessary load on the bearings and protects against dirt ingress into the system.',
            null, 'Japan', 'China', null, '83 mm', null, 'integrated', 'false'
            ),

            ('assets/images/spares_carriages/Neco B920AL 68 118mm.jpg', 'Neco B920AL 68 118mm', 'Neco', 1250, 3, 'CARRIAGE',
            'The Neco B920AL is a quality threaded bottom bracket designed for mountain and road bikes. The body is made of steel
            and the threaded cups are made of aluminum alloy (BSA thread standard 1.37x24T).',
            'Steel / Aluminum', 'Taiwan', 'Taiwan', 'silver', '68/118 mm', '302 g.', 'Threaded, 2 industrial bearings, squared axle', 'true'
            )
        </sql>
    </changeSet>


</databaseChangeLog>
