<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<databaseChangeLog
        xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
        xmlns="http://www.liquibase.org/xml/ns/dbchangelog"
        xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.liquibase.org/xml/ns/dbchangelog http://www.liquibase.org/xml/ns/dbchangelog/dbchangelog-3.1.xsd">

    <!-- Заполнение таблицы equipment шлемами -->
    <changeSet author="FeinIV" id="20220115_filling_equipment_table_HELMET">
        <sql>
            INSERT INTO equipment (
            img_addr, name, manufacturer, price, discount, type, description,
            material, development_country, manufacturer_country, color, size, weight, features, availability
            )
            VALUES
            ('assets/images/equipment_helmets/Casco Roadster m.V. Visor Antiscratch.jpg', 'Casco Roadster m.V. Visor Antiscratch', 'Casco', 15500, 5, 'HELMET',
            'Rugged helmet Casco Roadster m.V. Visor Antiscratch will provide maximum head protection when cycling,
            scooter or roller skates. Made using Monocoque Ultra technology (reinforced construction with steel rivets).
            The helmet has several ventilation holes located along the entire length from the forehead to the back of the head. The front openings are equipped
            insect net. The Casco-LOC fastening system provides a quick fixation of the helmet.',
            'Plastic / Steel / Aluminum', 'Germany', 'Taiwan', 'black', 'S (50-54 sm), M (55-57 sm), L (58-60 sm)', '200 g.', 'Visor Antiscratch, 2 reflective stripes', 'true'
            ),

            ('assets/images/equipment_helmets/Polisport XS Kids Spaceship.jpg', 'Polisport XS Kids Spaceship', 'Polisport', 2390, 0, 'HELMET',
            'Polisport XS Kids Lolipops is a children''s kit that includes a great safety helmet, drinking flask
            and a bottle holder. A rugged, in-mold helmet will protect your little one when riding a bike or scooter
            or a balance bike, and a bottle of water will help him quench his thirst. The helmet has 10 ventilation holes.',
            'Plastic / EPS', 'Portugal', 'Taiwan', 'blue', 'XS', '200 g.', 'In-Mold construction, 10 air vents, insect screen, micro-adjustment ring, reflective stickers, removable pads', 'false'
            ),

            ('assets/images/equipment_helmets/MV 26 (in mold).jpg', 'MV 26 (in mold)', 'MV', 1350, 5, 'HELMET',
            'MV 26 is a high impact safety helmet. Production material - a combination of polycarbonate with expanded polystyrene "In-Mold".
            Equipped with 22 ventilation holes. There is an adjustment for the head.',
            'Outer layer - polycarbonate, inner - expanded polystyrene', 'Taiwan', 'Taiwan', 'black-red', 'М (56-58 см), L (58-60 см)', '300 g.', 'In-Mold technology, 22 air vents', 'true'
            )
        </sql>
    </changeSet>

    <!-- Заполнение таблицы equipment рюкзаками -->
    <changeSet author="FeinIV" id="20220115_filling_equipment_table_BACKPACK">
        <sql>
            INSERT INTO equipment (
            img_addr, name, manufacturer, price, discount, type, description,
            material, development_country, manufacturer_country, color, size, weight, volume, features, availability
            )
            VALUES
            ('assets/images/equipment_backpack/Deuter Aviant Carry On 28.jpg', 'Deuter Aviant Carry On 28', 'Deuter', 12390, 10, 'BACKPACK',
            'The comfortable Deuter Aviant Carry On 28 backpack is designed for work and leisure trips. Its dimensions are completely
            comply with international hand luggage standards. Backpack volume: 28 liters. Weight - 1030 grams.',
            '600D PES / 420D PA', 'Germany', null, 'black, green, blue', '50 х 33 х 20 sm', '1300 g.', '28 liter', null, 'true'
            ),

            ('assets/images/equipment_backpack/Deuter StepOut 22.jpg', 'Deuter StepOut 22', 'Deuter', 6990, 0, 'BACKPACK',
            'The Deuter StepOut 22 is a roomy city backpack that is suitable for everyday work and sports activities. Backpack volume: 22 liters. Weight - 850 grams.',
            '600D PES / 300D PES Ripstop', 'Germany', null, 'black, green, blue, red', '46 х 30 х 19 sm', '850 g.', '22 liter', 'ventilated back Airstripes, adjustable waist strap with buckle', 'true'
            ),

            ('assets/images/equipment_backpack/Cube Pure 11L.jpg', 'Cube Pure 11L', 'Cube', 3500, 3, 'BACKPACK',
            'A compact backpack from the German company Cube, designed specifically for cycling. To avoid
            excessive sweating of the back, special mesh material shoulder straps and a breathable back layer have been developed
            Deuter Airstripes. The capacity of 11 liters is enough to pack a spare T-shirt, a set of tools and other small items.',
            'Nylon', null, null, 'grey-red, black-white', '42 x 23 x 10 sm', '540 g.', '11 liter', null, 'false'
            )
        </sql>
    </changeSet>

</databaseChangeLog>
