<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<databaseChangeLog
        xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
        xmlns="http://www.liquibase.org/xml/ns/dbchangelog"
        xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.liquibase.org/xml/ns/dbchangelog http://www.liquibase.org/xml/ns/dbchangelog/dbchangelog-3.1.xsd">

    <!-- Заполнение таблицы scooters внедорожными самокатами -->
    <changeSet author="FeinIV" id="12012022_filling_scooters_table_OFFROAD">
        <sql>
            INSERT INTO scooters (
            img_addr, name, manufacturer, price, discount, type, description,
            material, development_country, manufacturer_country, color, availability
            )
            VALUES
            ('assets/images/scooters_offroad/Rrampa C1 (230-200).jpg', 'Rrampa C1 (230-200)', 'Rrampa', 6990, 0, 'OFFROAD',
            'The Rrampa C1 scooter is an excellent city scooter that rolls perfectly thanks to the front shock absorber
            even on uneven pavement. The frame can withstand loads up to 100 kg',
            'Aluminum', 'Russia', 'China', 'black', 'true'
            ),

            ('assets/images/scooters_offroad/Novatrack Stamp N1 12ʺ (12STAMPN1.20).jpg', 'Novatrack Stamp N1 12ʺ (12STAMPN1.20)', 'Novatrack', 8780, 5, 'OFFROAD',
            'The off-road scooter Novatrack Stamp N1 provides the rider with comfortable conditions for moving around the city
            and flat rough terrain. Withstands loads up to 100 kg. Designed for children and teenagers aged 6+, as well as adults.',
            'Aluminum', 'China', 'China', 'white', 'false'
            ),

            ('assets/images/scooters_offroad/Razor Phase Two Dirt Scoot Diamond.jpg', 'Razor Phase Two Dirt Scoot Diamond', 'Razor', 24330, 18, 'OFFROAD',
            'The Razor Phase Two Dirt Scoot Diamond is a unique dirt scooter designed for stunts on rough terrain.
            Large, high-pressure (100 psi) inflatable wheels with strong tread provide excellent ground grip, while professional
            bearings guarantee excellent rolling. The deck of the scooter has a “useful” area of ​​13 x 37 cm with a total length of 90 cm.
            An impressive ground clearance of 9 cm makes it easy to overcome road irregularities. Handlebar: Y-shaped, chrome-molybdenum,
            height 95 cm from the ground. Scooter fork: reinforced, with threadless compression system. The steering wheel is fixed with a triple clamp. Brake:
            foot (back wing). The maximum load is 100 kg. Weight - 8 kg. Colour: silver.',
            'Aluminum', 'USA', 'China', 'silver', 'true'
            )
        </sql>
    </changeSet>

    <!-- Заполнение таблицы scooters городскими самокатами -->
    <changeSet author="FeinIV" id="12012022_filling_scooters_table_CITY">
        <sql>
            INSERT INTO scooters (
            img_addr, name, manufacturer, price, discount, type, description,
            material, development_country, manufacturer_country, color, availability
            )
            VALUES
            ('assets/images/scooters_city/Novatrack Polis 180 Pro (180.POLIS.9).jpg', 'Novatrack Polis 180 Pro (180.POLIS.9)', 'Novatrack', 5570, 0, 'CITY',
            'The Novatrack Polis 180 Pro scooter is an easy and affordable way to get around the city streets. with him you
            constantly on the move and give a daily payload to your body. The frame can withstand up to 100 kg of weight. The weight of the model is 4.5 kg.',
            'Aluminum', 'China', 'China', 'orange', 'true'
            ),

            ('assets/images/scooters_city/Novatrack Deft 230 Pro Brake (230BFS.DEFT.21).jpg', 'Novatrack Deft 230 Pro Brake (230BFS.DEFT.21)', 'Novatrack', 9430, 0, 'CITY',
            'The Novatrack Deft 230 Pro Brake scooter is an advanced urban model that you can ride comfortably
            even on uneven pavement. Equipped with front shock absorber and hand brake. The frame can withstand loads up to 100 kg. Weight - 5.5 kg.',
            'Aluminum', 'China', 'China', 'yellow', 'false'
            ),

            ('assets/images/scooters_city/Micro Luggage RS3.0.jpg', 'Micro Luggage RS3.0', 'Micro', 25780, 6, 'CITY',
            'A unique folding scooter, which is also a roomy suitcase with a volume of 33 liters.
            This "chemokat" is just the perfect solution for traveling around European cities! Inside there is a special
            compartment for tablet and laptop. The scooter has three polyurethane wheels - two front wheels with a diameter of 120 mm and
            rear 80 mm. Handlebar: retractable, height adjustable 89-98 cm. Deck dimensions - 10 x 35.5 cm. Ground clearance
            is 4 cm. Maximum frame load: up to 100 kg. Includes storage case and special
            replacement swivel pads (black for standard weight people, blue for light weights, red
            heavier for passengers). Black colour. Weight - 6.1 kg.',
            'Aluminum', 'Sweden', 'China', 'black', 'true'
            )
        </sql>
    </changeSet>

</databaseChangeLog>
