<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<databaseChangeLog
        xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
        xmlns="http://www.liquibase.org/xml/ns/dbchangelog"
        xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.liquibase.org/xml/ns/dbchangelog http://www.liquibase.org/xml/ns/dbchangelog/dbchangelog-3.1.xsd">

    <!-- Заполнение таблицы product_type_description амортизаторами -->
    <changeSet author="FeinIV" id="20220116_filling_product_type_description">
        <sql>
            INSERT INTO product_type_description (
            name, description
            )
            VALUES
            ('BICYCLES_WOMAN',
            'The main difference between a women''s bike and a mens bike is the use of a lowered frame, which guarantees
            a comfortable fit in any clothing. Manufacturers also seek to reduce the weight of the structure through the
            use of modern and more expensive metal alloys. Despite the limitations associated with these features, among
            women''s bikes you can choose a model for almost any style of riding - from pleasure to sports. The latter are
            in high demand among girls who actively monitor their physical form.'
            ),

            ('BICYCLES_CHILDREN',
            'Children''s bicycles are usually classified by wheel diameter: for kids from 1.5 to 3 years old, 12-inch
            wheels are suitable, for children from 2 to 4 years old - wheels with a diameter of 14 inches, 16-inch - for
            the age category from 3 to 5 years, and wheels 20- ty inches - for children under 9 years old. Also, in
            addition to the classic two- and three-wheeled bicycles, recently balance bikes have become more and more
            popular among young athletes, which are something in between scooters and a bicycle in design.'
            ),

            ('BICYCLES_ROAD',
            'Road bikes are a continuation of the hardtail line.
            The production is based on the manufacture of a classic rigid frame and fork made of high-strength steel
            alloy. Thanks to this technology, maximum acceleration is ensured without loss of travel (it is not
            extinguished by swinging the shock absorber). Road bikes are lighter than hardtails and therefore have better
            ride. Since this type is used mainly for driving on highway surfaces, the models are equipped with "bald"
            tires - they are narrower and more maneuverable. It is also important that the seating position on road bikes
            ensures that the cyclist''s back is in a comfortable position. Key models in the range come with a set of
            reflectors and protective fenders for the wheels and trunk.'
            ),

            ('BICYCLES_COMFORT',
            'The design of a comfortable bike, as the name suggests, is embodied with the goal of the most comfortable
            riding, mainly in urban and other "non-extreme" conditions. The characteristic features of such bicycles are
            a high seating position and a comfortable wide seat. Comfort bikes are divided into hardtails, with suspension
            forks, and cruisers, in the development of which the emphasis is primarily on design and aesthetics.'
            ),

            ('BICYCLES_GRAVEL',
            'The gravel bike is a new take on the concept of a comfortable road bike. What distinguishes it from classic
            road models is a longer wheelbase, larger tires, disc brakes and a frame geometry that is somewhere between
            road and MTB. A gravel bike can be called a crossover from the cycling world. It gives increased comfort and
            maneuverability at the cost of slightly increased weight and worse maneuverability. If you love the aesthetics
            of classic road bikes, but don''t think it''s a smart idea to buy all-terrain sports gear, a gravel bike is the way to go!'
            ),

            ('SCOOTERS_CITY',
            'For mobility in a big city, fast and useful movement, you should buy a city scooter - an actual type of
            transport in a metropolis. Models for city driving have a strong frame designed for different rider weights
            up to 100 kg, a handlebar adjustable for the appropriate height, polyurethane wheels with a diameter of 125
            to 200 mm and, of course, a modern design. The platform is ideal for a comfortable ride, many deck models have
            an anti-slip coating. Compact, practical and lightweight urban scooter, thanks to a reliable mechanism, can
            be easily folded for transportation in public transport. These are maneuverable and reliable units equipped
            with ergonomic grips, parking steps, foot or front brake.'
            ),

            ('SCOOTERS_OFFROAD',
            'You can ride a scooter not only on flat park paths, but also on rough terrain. For these purposes, there is
            a special model - an off-road scooter with increased cross-country ability. Such models have a steel frame
            and fork, fenders and reflective elements, a footrest, a trunk for small things. They have a fairly wide deck,
            inflatable wheels, durable aluminum rims, most often 12 inches in diameter. In urban conditions, an off-road
            scooter gives a good roll, and on rough terrain - increased cross-country ability. There are also models on
            polyurethane wheels, with an enlarged front rim. For different weight and height of the rider, children''s and
            teenage models, as well as an adult off-road scooter, are designed. SUVs are equipped with both rear and front brakes.'
            ),

            ('ACCESSORIES_TRUNK',
            'Bicycle racks are a device that makes it much easier to carry cargo on your bike. Now, when there are many
            varieties of them, the choice of this convenient accessory is not difficult. A non-separable bike rack is
            able to withstand a load of up to 25 kg, and also guarantee the possibility of holding a bike backpack on it.
            Manufacturers prefer to use steel, titanium and aluminum for luggage carriers. Steel trunks, with their strength
            and reliability, have a fairly large weight of the structure. Titanium are less common; they have a high cost
            and wear resistance. According to the types of fastening, bike racks are divided into 4 classes: a rack mounted
            on the seatpost with a clip; trunk attached to the rooster and the upper feathers of the rear triangle; with
            fastening only to feathers with the help of clamps; bolted to the seat tube. You can choose a bike rack for
            any type from any line of bikes.'
            ),

            ('ACCESSORIES_PUMP',
            'Maintaining the required predetermined pressure in the chambers is impossible without a pump. It is a
            mandatory attribute of a cyclist. Among the types of pumps are stationary and portable. Each type has
            advantages. A stationary pump will be useful and convenient for use at home or in a bike shop, while a
            portable one is on the go. Modern bicycle pumps are almost universal: the presence of two heads - "presto"
            and auto - allow them to be used on any models of bicycles.'
            ),

            ('EQUIPMENT_HELMET',
            'Alas, no one is immune from falls and injuries. Fans of extreme riding in the style of trial, street, freeride,
            downhill and other types of it know the need to protect themselves. Bicycle helmets are reliable protection
            against drops and bumps. Made of high-strength plastic, they have a streamlined shape that seems to "cut" the
            air. Many types and types of helmets will help you choose the best option.'
            ),

            ('ACCESSORIES_BACKPACK',
            'A bicycle backpack differs from a regular city backpack, first of all, by its anatomical shape and the presence
            of a special breathable back that removes moisture and heat. Also, such backpacks, as a rule, are equipped
            with a special compartment for a hydrator, eliminating the need for a cyclist to carry a water bottle or flask
            with them. The size of the backpack is selected depending on the tasks and the amount of equipment carried.
            Manufacturers produce models from small ones - up to 10 liters, and up to large 30-liter options.'
            )

        </sql>
    </changeSet>

</databaseChangeLog>
