<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<databaseChangeLog
        xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
        xmlns="http://www.liquibase.org/xml/ns/dbchangelog"
        xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.liquibase.org/xml/ns/dbchangelog http://www.liquibase.org/xml/ns/dbchangelog/dbchangelog-3.1.xsd">

    <!-- Заполнение таблицы accessories багажниками -->
    <changeSet author="FeinIV" id="13012022_filling_accessories_table_TRUNKS">
        <sql>
            INSERT INTO accessories (
            img_addr, name, manufacturer, price, discount, type, description,
            material, development_country, manufacturer_country, color, size, features, availability
            )
            VALUES
            ('assets/images/accessories_trunks/Stels 24-28ʺ BLF-H8.jpg', 'Stels 24-28ʺ BLF-H8', 'Stels', 1390, 0, 'TRUNK',
            'The excellent bike rack BLF-H8 is made of lightweight and durable aluminum alloy. Adjustable
            the design of the racks allows it to be used on a variety of bikes with wheels from 24 to 26 inches.
            A special clip on the springs will help fix a small bag or jacket. There is a mount for a tail light. Black colour.',
            'Aluminum', 'Russia', 'Russia', 'black', '24-28 inches', 'For bicycles with 24-28 inches wheels. Height regulation', 'true'
            ),

            ('assets/images/accessories_trunks/ZLYJ-A.jpg', 'ZLYJ-A', 'ZLYJ', 700, 0, 'TRUNK',
            'Standard aluminum trunk. Suitable for bikes with 24" to 28" wheels.
            The maximum weight declared by the manufacturer is up to 25 kg, but practice proves that the weight can be much more.',
            'Aluminum', 'Taiwan', 'Taiwan', 'silver', '24-28 inches', 'For bicycles 24-28 inches.', 'false'
            ),

            ('assets/images/accessories_trunks/Stels BLF-H27-3 20-28ʺ.jpg', 'Stels BLF-H27-3 20-28ʺ', 'Stels', 1490, 0, 'TRUNK',
            'Comfortable and high-quality console rack Stels BLF-H27-3 will be a great solution for your bike. It is suitable for
            various bicycles with a wheel diameter of 20-28ʺ. Equipped with a quick-release seatpost mount and two
            adjustable posts. Made from aluminium. Black color.',
            'Aluminum', 'Russia', 'Russia', 'black', '20-28 inches', 'For bicycles 20-28 inches. Height regulation', 'true'
            )
        </sql>
    </changeSet>

    <!-- Заполнение таблицы accessories насосами -->
    <changeSet author="FeinIV" id="13012022_filling_accessories_table_PUMP">
        <sql>
            INSERT INTO accessories (
            img_addr, name, manufacturer, price, discount, type, description,
            material, development_country, manufacturer_country, color, features, availability
            )
            VALUES
            ('assets/images/accessories_pumps/SKS Injex Lite Zoom, grey, plastic, telescopic.jpg', 'SKS Injex Lite Zoom, grey, plastic, telescopic', 'SKS', 1890, 0, 'PUMP',
            'Do you like mountain trips or do you prefer trekking bikes? At the same time, the tires are subject to sufficient
            big load. To protect yourself from unpleasant situations while driving and ensure a feeling of comfort,
            Tires must always be inflated. Take with you the model of the compact plastic
            pump is convenient, it is easily attached to the frame, its weight is only 175 grams, and it will not weigh down the bike. The pump has
            a universal head with valves and clamps for the plug, which prevent dust and dirt from getting inside the wheel, thereby damaging it.',
            'Plastic', 'Germany', 'Germany', 'black', null, 'true'
            ),

            ('assets/images/accessories_pumps/Giyo GF-34.jpg', 'Giyo GF-34', 'Giyo', 1990, 5, 'PUMP',
            'The Giyo GF-34 manual floor pump is a profitable and necessary purchase for your garage or workshop.
            With it, you can quickly pump up the wheel of the bike. The body is made of steel. The handle has an ergonomic
            T-shape. The pump is equipped with a long rubber hose and a Presta/Schrader universal valve (FV/AV). Color: silver/black.',
            'Steel / Plastic', 'China', 'China', 'silver / black', 'Presta/Schrader (FV/AV)', 'false'
            ),

            ('assets/images/accessories_pumps/BBB AirSteel BFP-27.jpg', 'BBB AirSteel BFP-27', 'BBB', 3790, 10, 'PUMP',
            'The BBB AirSteel BFP-27 is a manual floor pump that is great for workshops or the garage. Corps and
            The base is made of solid steel. Height - 67 cm. At the bottom there is a built-in pressure gauge with bar / psi scales.
            The large T-handle is made of plastic. The rubber hose is 90 cm long. At the end of the hose there is a universal
            block valve (suitable for Dunlop/Presta/Schrader valves). Maximum delivery pressure: 11 bar / 160 psi. Colors: yellow, black.',
            'Steel / Plastic', 'Taiwan', 'Taiwan', 'yellow', 'Dunlop/Presta/Schrader, manometer', 'true'
            )
        </sql>
    </changeSet>

</databaseChangeLog>
